germancarscene.com 2016-03-15

# Privacy Statement - German Car Scene

## [Privacy Statement](http://germancarscene.com/privacy-statement/ "Permalink to Privacy Statement")

Posted on 14th March, 2009 by admin  
Filed in | [Leave a comment](http://germancarscene.com/privacy-statement/#comments)

Please read this statement regarding our blogs. If you have questions please contact us.

Email Addresses

You may choose to add your email address to our contact list via the forms on our websites. We agree that we will never share your email with any third party other than the providers of such services. We don’t currently send advertising via email, but in the future our email may contain advertisements and we may send dedicated email messages from our advertisers without revealing your email addresses to them. If you have any problem removing your email address please contact us.

Ownership of Information

GermanCarScene is the sole owner of any information collected on our websites.

Comments/Message Boards

GermanCarScene contains comment sections. We actively monitor these comments and the information on them is for entertainment purposes only. If a comment is deemed to be inappropriate in any way, we may delete it at our discretion.  
Cookies

We may assign cookies to our readers in order to manage their preferences and ensure the site’s functionality. This data is not shared with any third party. Accessing our websites is not dependent on accepting cookies and all major browsers allow you to disable cookies if you wish.

Third Party Cookies

GermanCarScene and its advertisers may also use ad network providers to help present advertisements on other Web sites. These ad network providers use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies on your computer to help present, better target, and measure the effectiveness of their advertisements, using data gathered over time and across their networks of Web pages to determine or predict the characteristics and preferences of their audience. GermanCarScene may share certain non-personally identifiable information about you as a GermanCarScene user (such as user age and zip code) with certain ad network providers, to help them deliver more relevant advertisements through their ad networks. The use of cookies, web beacons and other ad network providers is subject to their own privacy policies, not that of GermanCarScene.

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.co.uk/privacy_ads.html). Google use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit their website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and would like to know your options in relation to not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

Traffic Reports

Our industry-standard traffic reporting records IP addresses, Internet service provider information, referrer strings, browser types and the date and time pages are loaded. We use this information in the aggregate only to provide traffic statistics to advertisers and to figure out which features and editorials are most popular.  
Legal proceedings

We will make every effort to preserve user privacy but GermanCarScene may need to disclose information when required by law.

Business Transitions

If GermanCarScene is acquired by or merges with another firm, the assets of our websites, including personal information, will likely be transferred to the new firm.  
Links

GermanCarScene frequently link to other websites. We are not responsible for the content or business practices of these websites. When you leave our websites we encourage you to read the destination site’s privacy policy. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by GermanCarScene.  
Notification of Changes

When GermanCarScene makes changes to this privacy policy we will post those changes here.  
Contact Information

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.
